[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
\What’s your sex trip these days?
\Do you want to revisit the erotic films of the ’90s
\that awakened your sensuality?
\I’m Jamilla Obispo, and I’ll be sharing with you
\some provocative films
that once heated things up and stirred your burning desires.
This is Pinoy Sexy Classics.
Movies that made you grow up.
First on our hot, hot list of sexy throwback films is
the 1995 erotic drama by Tata Esteban, “Gayuma.”
Starring the incredibly sexy and beautiful Amanda Page.
Also starring Maritoni Fernandez, Julio Diaz, and Jay Manalo.
You’ll definitely be hooked by the heat and the story that “Gayuma” brings,
because of the challenges our characters will go through…
As its poster says,
“Don’t come closer if you don’t want to be tempted.”
But being the rebellious ones that they are,
our characters gave in to temptation and truly…
got bewitched.
Give me back my husband.
Rubing is mine.
How about the girl?
I
don’t
care.
How about us?
Don't worry. I got you.
Whew! That scene was really hot.
Now, let’s take a peek at another provocative film.
Starring the fantasy and object of desire of many men in the ’90s,
Rosanna Roces.
This sexy film is “Miss Kristina Moran,”
directed by Eric Quizon in 1999.
He is also one of the actor in this film.
Also part of the cast are Raymond Bagatsing
and Albert Martinez.
The film follows a bold woman,
who is a star performer at a nightclub.
Let’s take a peek at Tina Moran’s exciting sexual escapades
with the different men who became part of
her wild and hot journey…
Don’t stop, I’m cumming.
Did you just come?
You’ve already come a lot, but I haven’t finished yet.
Put it in. We can still do it.
Make me cum.
June, stop. I'm begging you.
June, stop!
You fucker! What do you mean stop?
This is all you want right?
Okay, don't stop. If you pull it out, I'm going to kill you!
You're overreacting!
I'm just tickling your ears not your balls.
That’s really my weak spot.
I’m going to do something to you that's even more ticklish.
What are you going to do?
Just drive.
Hey, calm down.
Before we take a peek at the next film on our list,
we have a little challenge first.
This is the 90s Pose of Fame,
where I’ll pose the different characters,
depending on what I draw.
Okay, the first walk I’ll be doing is… “Beach Babe.”
Before I continue with my Pose of Fame,
I’ll first introduce you to our next titillating film.
It’s about a wealthy filmmaker
who became paralyzed from the waist down.
Right from the very beginning,
you’ll already be heating up over his fantasies…
Let’s take a peek.
Don't fight it.
You’re enjoying it.
You’re enjoying what he is doing.
You also want to lick his body.
Stop it!
This hot movie is “Ang Kabit ni Mrs. Montero,”
directed by award-winning director Peque Gallaga,
and starring Edu Manzano and Sunshine Cruz.
Also starring Patricia Javier and Gardo Versoza.
Your passions will definitely be set ablaze
by the steamy scenes you’ll see in this film…
and, now it’s time for me to draw
my next 90s Pose of Fame.
Oh, this walk is perfect for our movie—
“CEO’s Mistress.”
So, of course, it has to be fierce
but with a wealthy, sophisticated vibe.
Okay, let me try it.
Let’s revisit another 2001 film.
It’s about two people who met, fell in love,
and held on to hope until…
“Sa Huling Paghihintay.”
It was directed by Erik Matti
and stars Bernard Palanca
and Rica Peralejo.
This is a sweet and sexy movie
that will make you feel the butterflies
and turn up the heat
with its seductive scenes…
Okay, it’s time for our next 90s Pose of Fame.
I wonder what I’ll draw.
Hopefully, it’s an easy one.
Oh, this is cute. “Campus Heartthrob.”
Since I'm prepared,
I already have here some books and a backpack.
We’re gonna do it.
Our next film is yet another masterpiece
from veteran director Erik Matti.
It’s a sexy crime drama film
that was first released in 1999,
starring the irresistibly alluring Sunshine Cruz
and the handsome Albert Martinez.
This is Gene.
Slowly.
Is he asleep?
Dolor? Dolor!
Dolor!
We're wasting water.
We should report all these bystander.
I already told you to do it tomorrow.
Go ahead. I'm doing something now
I'll finish it first.
Also in the film are Raymond Bagatsing, Ace Espinosa,
Jaime Fabregas, Ryan Eigenmann,
and John Arcilla,
the abusive husband of to the character of Sunshine
Sorry.
We’re definitely going to witness some intense scenes
here in… “Ekis.”
This is our last 90s Pose of Fame.
I’m getting excited to see
what kind of pose I’ll be doing this time.
90s Bombshell. Wow.
I can definitely pull this off!
Since we’re revisiting all these hot, hot films
that heated things up for us,
I’ll also revisit some things
I’ve done in the past.
So, I’m at the hot seat now.
Let's play "Never have I ever."
Okay, apparently we’re starting with Level 1.
I’ll hold up all ten fingers
and put one down every time
I’ve done something mentioned in the questions.
If I have all ten fingers down by the end of the game,
I’ll have to face a consequence!
Okay, first is all about my career life.
Never have I ever forgotten my lines during an intense scene.
I have.
Never have I ever laughed during a dramatic scene.
Never.
Never have I ever intentionally messed up a kissing scene
so we could do it again and kiss my co-star again.
I have never.
Never have I ever forgotten the name of someone I was filming a scene with.
Yes, I have.
Never have I ever genuinely felt butterflies during a romantic scene.
I have.
Let’s take a peek at our next titillating film.
Once again directed by Erik Matti,
we have Mark Anthony Fernandez,
who works at a hardware store
and admires a nightclub dancer
played by… Rica Peralejo.
This 2001 sexy crime movie is
the final installment in the Ekis film series.
And although it has the same theme,
we’ll be seeing a different story here in…
“Dos Ekis.”
You’re definitely going to heat up
with the provocative scenes you’ll see here.
I am already starting to feel hot.
We’re moving on to Level 2
of our Never Have I Ever.
Questions: Behind the Glam!
This is getting nerve-racking.
Level two.
Never have I ever received an expensive gift from a fan.
I have never.
Never have I ever received an indecent proposal.
Yes. I have.
Never have I ever watched one of my romantic scenes with my family.
I have never.
Never have I ever gone on a date with someone I met on set.
I have.
Never have I ever gotten jealous of a co-worker.
I have. I got jealous.
Next on our sexy, titillating list
is a captivating 1998 film.
This is “Dama de Noche,”
starring the incredibly hot Ynez Veneracion
as a woman who was mistreated and abused
and eventually became addicted to sex…
Also starring Mark Gil
as Ynez’s husband.
Those scenes were incredibly hot!
But, oh no… we’re already at Level 3
of Never Have I Ever!
This time, we’re talking about matters of the heart.
Oh my God!
Never have I ever fallen in love with a co-star.
I have never
Never have I ever had a secret relationship..
I have.
Never have I ever made the first move to get my crush’s attention.
Of course, I have!
Never have I ever had a crush on a fan.
I have never.
Never have I ever been dumped because my partner got jealous of my co-star.
Almost. But never.
With that, I still have three fingers.
Are you still thirsty for desire?
Don’t worry, because I still have one more sexy throwback film
to share with you,
and I’m sure it will…
caress…
your burning desires.
“Bayad Puri” is a 1997 sexy drama
directed by Joel Lamangan.
Starring the incredibly hot
Gary Estrada, Dindi Gallardo, and Raymond Bagatsing.
Ruby Moreno and Jay Manalo.
Chin Chin Gutierrez and Richard Quan.
And since that’s our last movie
on our sexy throwback list,
my Never Have I Ever is getting even more intense.
Level 4… let’s talk about sex!
Never have I ever watched my own sex scene and masturbated.
I have never.
Never have I ever had sex in a public place.
I have.
Never have I ever had sex with someone of the same gender.
Just kiss.
Never have I ever fulfilled my sexual fantasy.
I have never done my sexual fantasy.
Even if I didn't lose, I'll still give you a dance bonus.
Are you guys ready?
Did you feel that first spark of heat
come rushing back
when you first awakened to your sensuality?
I hope I helped you relive
the excitement
and the rush of your burning desires.
And again, I’m Jamilla Obispo.
This is Pinoy Sexy Classics. Movies that made you grow up.